I want to discuss
with all the accused brothers
how you can view your insurance. You
can't view your insurance, but you can also get renewal support. If
you go to the portal for your transaction,
you'll
get an SMS option. If you select this option, the
customer will receive both the code and the available code, allowing them to
view their non-renewal code. We've seen some people
whose insurance has expired during this long period,
or who can't
reach their vehicle.
I'm Sure has
released a new app for vehicle inspections. It has many benefits.
You customers can view this and
can refund their expired inspection. This
also eliminates the large network offline service. Those who have
n't gone there to do this can
themselves open the insurance application,
upload photos, and send them.
I don't need any video recording. I just send a photo of a vehicle, so
our people and our
Aarambh colleagues will help. If you have any problems,
you can contact me.
As soon as your photo is uploaded,
we will get the inspection approval and you
can book the policy which is mandatory. So please
use I am sure as much as possible to book your business.
If any vehicle breaks down, then next
like please.
Now I would like to say a
few words about compulsory personal accident cover. If
my expert Mr. Gaurav
Khanna, who is our support underwriter,
says a few words to me, then the problem of
this page will become clear.
Gaurav ji, career writer,
yes, thank you sir, you,
yes, now speak and Ajit ji, compulsory
personal accidental cover, personal accident
insurance,
you must be aware that in the year 2018, as per the
direction of the Supreme Court, IRDA has made
this cover mandatory for every
vehicle officer, whether he is
taking it or not, it is mandatory.
In compulsory personal accident, every
person has a sum of Rs. 15 lakhs, in
this, his death, permanent total
disability
and the proof of councilor reader is there.
Many times we have seen compulsory personal
We club accident cover with the given waist
or consider it to be the same thing. It is
very
important that personal accident cover is an essential cover.
It cannot be taken only in those accidents.
If a person
already has another personal accident cover
available, does he have more than two
options on which he has
taken accident cover or does he
not have a driving license or is a company.
Apart from this, compulsory personal accident cover
is required for everyone. Apart from this, optional personal
accident cover for passenger is another
passenger cover which is optional and
gives confirmed accident cover in only two lockers.
We should inform each of our customers about both of them
properly. As our
friend Siddharth ji said, what is seen
sells. So, in the same context, I would
like to add from my side that along with being aware, it is
also necessary to give knowledge about it to every customer. Some things are
told verbally, some are definitely shown.
Now I will tell you about the things that are required in the coming days.
Next flight please
is Audi Point Two Wheeler Tasty brothers.
For this, we have segmented the insurance premium of each two wheeler i.e.
its premium, that is,
it will not be affected by increasing or decreasing the subscription to TV channels,
whether it is Activa or Royal
Enfield, so you can see that for the 5 year
option, its insurance price has been fixed at Rs. 349,
similarly
for the option older than 1 year, its price has been
fixed at Rs. 249, this process has been done
for the purpose of making the insurance very simple,
we
can understand this through an example, as you can see, the
manufacturer is Hero Honda Motor Car
and on the other side there is Royal Enfield model and it is
Royal Enfield Classic 350, the
RTO ID of one in Lucknow and one in Patna vehicle can
also be between Rs. 20,000 to Rs. 25,000 in Hero Motor Corp,
it can go up to Rs.
26,000 in Royal Enfield case, there will be no
change on our content premium, it will
remain fixed at Rs. 349, similarly the third party
premium which is third party  It has been
determined by IRDA, it changes
in both of them as per their press TV,
828 is 1349,
a comprehensive premium of Vitex 1240 and
1761, within this you will leave the compulsory personal
accident which I told you in the previous side,
we will clear it, 1683 will
come to 2204, I would like to reiterate again,
this compulsory personal accident cover
is mandatory for every vehicle owner,
next flight
soon, when our option becomes more than a year
old, the same Chinese voter, Royal
Enfield Pleasure Classic 350
ID is also getting changed at RTO Lucknow Patna, there is
no change in its DC rate for us,
249 is 249 pick,
according to the decision of duty of 35mm option, tech and
compulsory personal accident news which is
necessary, next flight happened, so
as told, it is
very important to give knowledge to all our customers so that whatever is
told will be sold well, so in
this series you must have heard earlier that
every vehicle used to be insured only two  It was of one
type, either it was a low principal
policy i.e. body OTP or both,
so there were always some expressions in it, to
cover those expressions,
some DON'T covers have been fixed according to the time, the
customers can save their expenses by taking Madam,
as you all know, every vehicle has to pay a
claim at the time of accident, the
owner of the vehicle suffers the most,
as you know, the
owner of the vehicle has to pay 50% depreciation on the plastic passes,
similarly, there is
30% depreciation on the fiber passes which the
owner has to pay and the
parts of the meter which are changed like
iron parts or inside it, the administrator of Eminem, on that the
older the development, the more the
depreciation will be, the more he will have to pay the
depreciation,
if we tell our customers the
DON'T of Herodih station, they
take this Madam, after that at the time of plane the
customers do not need to pay anything in the name of depreciation from their pocket,
know if in his vehicle  There will be
no decoration charge on it for Rs. 5000.
I will add Engine Protect Plus to this
as we all know that whenever the
vehicle gets into waterlogged areas where a
lot of water gets collected, it
stops and when we
try to start it, it gets
fried, then that water gets absorbed inside
and the engine gets damaged and the engine gets damaged by the
evening. The
replacement was definitely opened and re-fastened and
many parts inside the engine had to be replaced.
In the old times, whenever there were any defects, the
customer had to pay for them from his own pocket
but Engine Protect Plus is such an
add on that after taking it, the
customers get cover from their own pocket
even in England time. If the
engine oil of the car gets leaked from the hydrostatic valve
and after that, when the car gets run, it gets
leaked and this type of damage gets
covered in the insurance by taking this option.
About this, Return to Invoice Return
to Invoice as the name suggests  It is understandable
that going back to the invoice,
suppose someone has insured a vehicle for Rs. 10 lakh
and when he
bought the vehicle it was worth Rs. 15 lakh, today if his
vehicle gets stolen, he is
covered up to the sum insured i.e. Rs. 10 lakh on the insurance,
but if he has taken cover for a return of Rs.
15 lakh, then
he will
get the full claim of Rs. 15 lakh at the time of insurance,
apart from this
if he has incurred
any expense in getting the vehicle registered
or whatever expenses he has incurred in getting the vehicle insured,
all those expenses are also covered in the return to invoice
and after this we see tyre protect i.e.
tyre protection, if
during an accident all other tyres are
damaged then that is also covered normally
but if there is
only damage to the tyre in the vehicle, if the tyre gets damaged then there is no loss
to all, if there is only
damage to the tyre then it should be taken, then if he did
not subscribe at that time  It
means that
a roadside assistant is given to the children, that is, a cover for the problems faced by the customer while travelling on the road,
suppose the customer's car gets exhausted by the time of going
or the battery is not working,
he may
need a jumpstart taxi to go somewhere, at the
time of accident or it is night time,
he has to stay in a hotel, all these types
of problems are
covered under the roadside assistance, that today or during a festival,
if a vehicle owner meets with an accident, the time taken to get
his vehicle repaired on time, the
pension expenses incurred during that time are paid in Yuvraj Test and
after a minimum time,
give Rs. 11 and if it takes
more time to repair or recover the vehicle, then the
customer should be paid his claim on a per day basis.
If during an accident some personal belongings of the customer are lost or stolen inside the vehicle, or if they are not found, then
their bill payment can be done. If the customer has taken a loan for
personal benefit, then their anger can be
calmed and covered.  A key
protector cover is provided, meaning the protection of the key.
In today's time of technology, all the vehicles have
immobilizer technology. You must have
heard of the key which is used inside the car, that is, the key
can be opened with the same key. If the key is broken, then the
entire lock is broken or the entire
cloth has to be sold to the factory and a new key has to be
made. If at that time a key
protector cover was purchased, which is
available at a very minimal price. By taking these measures,
all those
claims are paid at the time of loss. So our
aim here is to provide as many
protection add-ons as possible which are available in the market
or it is necessary to inform the customer.
If we tell you, only then will he be able to
decide well whether he needs it
or not. The
second benefit is that tomorrow at the time of claim,
when the claim is made with them, then
they will understand what
add-ons they had purchased at
that time due to which they are getting so much damage or which dots they did not pay due to which today they have to pay for them from their pocket.  If the
customer does not ask you at your centre why
you did not tell us this, then it is
our duty that
while selling the policy to them, we should
tell them as many of our I don't options available to them. Give them that
when you make a transaction with your life partner as
mentioned in the portal, then the
add-ons which are
applicable on the page in the product will be
visible there as per our underwriting guidelines. You
can see their freedom in the PM breakup below by selecting 'don't'. If there is any
product or on any S, suppose the
option is very old, it is possible that there is
no advisability there, then we have added them and
according to their one,
click on it in the product itself through technology so that you can easily understand
which dots are possible to be given to us while selling the policy to the customer.
Next Flight Production and Indian
Protector. I told you in the previous side that
in our Northern Grid, there is no need to give any depreciation
on plastic parts and metal parts while getting the vehicle repaired. If
you have them, then anyway right now
But there is no addition and
friends, in the repair of the vehicle, there is the cost of labor, there is
no production of constipation in that too, so this
is basically in the context of the text,
New Delhi station and metro text, effective
wages and definition of plastic part, as it is
fifty percent, we have
more than 56 hundred cashless shops across the country, due to which
many times I have heard that people are
worried that how will they get cashless shops,
but at the time of accident, whenever people
call our toll free number and
tell them the location of their accident, then our
customer care officer will tell them the address of
all the carats of Research Ashley near them,
Dad Virat Kohli will be
told so that they can also
help you as much as possible at the time of accident.
Apart from this, even while selling the policy,
if you want, on our full ICC website of this law
board, you can see the list of our cashless
shops nearest to your area, your
district, your blog.
Now, engine products, as I mentioned,
production of Tarapith engine, hydrostatic,
local mechanic and in case of damage,
all the covers including plant rain water drinking, are available.
Next  Flight will be
repaired soon and to you. Thank you Gaurav ji.
Thank you very much for sharing such informative
information with everyone, which despite being
on the portal, we still did
not know about it. I hope today you have
explained it in such detail that people have
understood how much
information is available on the portal and they will
definitely pass it on to their customers. Next, let us
tell you about Hotspot. This
product, which I have been saying again and again,
is a good product. It is a cash benefit product for special health insurance
benefits progress,
which you can use
anywhere. I will explain
further on this side
how you can use it.
Next, please note
that the ICC Loot History Fund has been launched for daily
payouts for the candidates
who are daily wage earners,
who go with you to the tea shop every day as customers,
for all of them.
I would
like to inform you that the age of the person should be between 18 to
56 years for whom
you can avail this policy. You
can determine this.  That they should
determine the construction work that their income should be between ₹500 to
₹10 thousand, anyone
can select this policy
for themselves, if they take a policy of ₹500 for 5 days coverage, then
this policy will cost them around three
hundred and fifty, maximum up
to ₹500, so you should
check it once on this portal and once you
enter your date of birth, there is no need for any paper in it,
only no one will ask you for photo
etc.,
you just have to enter your Aadhar
platform details on this portal, such as your name,
enter your date of birth correctly and this
policy will be given to you
Ajit, in this we will mix its hospitalization, so
both accident and disease
are covered, due to which if you are admitted
in any other hospital, whether it is
related to ICC Lamba or not, it is not necessary on this,
you just have to take the discharge scheme voucher from there,
which you will have to submit to us,
along with it you will have to submit the Aadhar copy and the
copy of your passbook, Amit, we will
send you the problem, it is not necessary that
you go anywhere  Also in any hospital, which is
in the IS A box, I am telling you again, you
can also add edit elections in it,
so you should definitely take this policy, my
brother and baby, keep this policy with you,
whatever problem
you have with the facilities in it, it is also related to
this system, you people should definitely take this policy once,
this is a very good policy
of SEAL Commando, this time it is available on your portal,
where you go and click on motor insurance,
next to it you can click on health,
this policy is available there, its name is
its fund policy, this is not a health policy,
but if you fall ill and
you do not work for 5 days, Sabir, if you did
not go to work and you have taken cover for it, then
you will get this amount which you have come to Delhi,
we will tweet it to your account,
next you please
come, today many of our rap scenes are
related to states, some from Bihar, some
from Uttarakhand and some from
Uttar Pradesh, I welcome everyone again
and after watching today's
program, many questions must be swirling in everyone's mind,
I will share some of my tips one by one  I would like to
tell you that first of all I would
like to call Rishi Pal ji Singh ji from Etawah,
he has some questions for Rishi Pal that if you are
listening to my voice then turn on your video audio
and ask your question
that hello sir I am Rishi Pal Singh hello sir hello please
tell me your question
that I am from Duba in the city and electricity is free since 2015
this my question through survey is that on the
policy which we make from CSC you will
get subsidy on gas cylinder from the dealer
because most of the dealers say that you could
not get the policy from us,
you have got the best policy made, then
we will not be able to give you cashless facility on such a policy, the
translation of this is Rishi Pal ji your question is absolutely
correct I will ask Gaurav ji would you
like to answer this Gaurav ji as
I understood that customers are
not able to get cashless facility, so I would like to tell
that our ingredient is subscription,
if you feel like it or not then at that
time you can contact our officer
and at that time he will provide you full
assistance  It will be done and I would like to tell you one more thing
that if you talk to the customer care officer on the graph, they will
tell you about such a place where we will have it and you should
not face any problem while going there, then
I think you must have got the answer as per
Rishi Pal ji,
yes sir, absolutely sir,
thank you very much sir, thank you, thank you now
yours and I will go now, the next person Raza
Abbas ji would like to join us from Lucknow,
these soils are also respected, Jahan ji,
you turn on your audio-video, you can run,
Shri Radha ji's question came in front of me,
Gaurav ji, I would still like to add
Jahan ji's question soon, sir, hello sir,
hello sir,
yes sir, thank you very much, I got the opportunity to
join the tribal son-in-law's line meeting,
our Ghagra was that if we make a
change on any vehicle, then
two people are given along with the vehicle, for
how many years can we continue to take the benefit of it, like in
this we
made the payment of the product premium, our pimples are born, till
when can we take the benefit of it and it is
good that you asked, I will tell Gaurav ji
that he should answer this and as I
While subscribing,
within each product, according to each model and many
parties, if appointed accordingly, then it can be added
to the car for five years,
but if there is N0 in any of them, then it gets
entered inside that, that is, Jhal Jhal.